Playful Kiss (Naughty Kiss) YouTube version
イタズラなキスYou Tube 版
Subtitles brought to you by the PKer team at Viki
Subtitles created by the PKer team at www.Viki
Episode 1 Newlywed Morning
第一話　新婚の朝
I realize this even more these days,
最近　日に日に感じるの
when I open up my eyes in the morning,
朝 目が覚めて－
I'm so happy at the mere fact that Seung Jo is next to me.
スンジョが横にいるってだけでとても幸せ
Though it's already been a year since we got married, I still can't believe it.
結婚して1年になるけどいまだに信じられないわ
Does Seung Jo feel that way too?
スンジョも一緒かな？
Good morning.
グッドモーニング
Did you sleep well?
よく寝られた？
Your stare is blinding.
おまえに見つめられるとまぶしいよ
Even more so than the sunlight.
朝日よりもね
It's Sunday.
日曜だし
Let's sleep some more.
もうちょっと寝よう
I have to get up.
私 起きなきゃ
Everyone went on a trip and it's been a while since we've spent time together, just the two of us.
みんな旅行に行って二人っきりで過ごすの久しぶりだね
I'm going to make Seung Jo's breakfast myself.
私がスンジョの朝食つくるわ
Just 5 minutes.
あと5分
Fine, just 5 minutes?
あと5分ね
Did you sleep well, Seung Jo?
よく寝られた　スンジョ？
The sun hasn't even come up yet, why did you set the alarm so early?!
まだ日も昇ってないぞなのに何でこんなに早くアラームをセットしたんだ？
Don't stare up at me with those swollen eyes!
そんな腫れぼったい目で見つめるな
Everyone went on a trip, so it's a Sunday with just Seung Jo.
みんな旅行に行って スンジョと二人の日曜日
Enjoy a perfect English breakfast just like in the movies.
映画みたいにイングリッシュ・ブレックファーストを食べて－
Clean the house with Seung Jo until it's sparkling clean!
スンジョと一緒におうちをピカピカに掃除して－
I want to show everyone the image of a perfect daughter-in-law.
みんなに完璧な嫁の姿を見せたいの
I also plan on watching a romantic comedy with Seung Jo.
スンジョと一緒にロマンチック・コメディーも見て－
I'm so looking forward to today!
今日がとても楽しみなの！
What are you looking for, new bride?
若奥さん 何をお探しで？
New bride!
若奥さん？
Me?!
私のこと？
Then what other new bride is there?
他に誰かいます？
New bride?
若奥さん？
That's right, I'm a new bride!
そうよ　私若奥さんよ
It's fresh, what do you think?
新鮮よ　どう？
If you boil and marinate it, it's really good!
ゆがいてマリネにしたら 美味しいですよ
Your husband will enjoy it!
ご主人が喜ぶわよ
Please give this to me.
これ下さい
And this one, and that one, and that one! Please give me one of each!
じゃあこれと　あれと　それと ひとつずつ下さい
New bride!
若奥さん
Yes?
はい
Go enjoy these with your husband. They're apples.
ご主人とどうぞ　リンゴです
Thank you!
ありがとうございます
No, no, no!
ダメ　ダメ　ダメ！
What are you doing?!
何だよ？
Why are you eating this? Do you know how important breakfast is?
何でこれを食べてるの？朝食がいかに大事か知ってる？
Then again, where did you go at the break of dawn?
なら 夜明け前に どこに行ってたんだ？
Are you going to make a feast for breakfast?
朝食にご馳走をつくるのか？
Just leave it up to me. Do you know how much I've looked forward to it being just the two of us?
まかせておいて二人っきりのこの日を－どれだけ楽しみにしていたかわかる？
Do you think you can do it by yourself?
一人で出来るのか？
You're not going to starve me, are you?
俺を飢え死にさせないよな？
But I'm still a new bride.
でもまだ私　若奥さんだし－
There's no way I'll starve my hubby.
旦那様を飢え死に させるわけないでしょ
New bride?
若奥さん？
Hubby?
旦那様
I'll prepare breakfast, so hubby, please go wash up.
朝食の準備をするから　旦那様身支度をしてきて
Hey.
おい
Are you trying to play the role of newlyweds just like in dramas?
ドラマみたいな新婚さんをするつもりか？
We are newlyweds.
私たち新婚よ
Stop dilly-dallying. Hurry and go up.
グズグズしてないで 早く上に行って
I put the laundry in the washer so start it for me too!
洗濯機すぐに回しといてくれる？
Let's just eat out.
食べに出ようよ
Please just go up.
いいから上に行ってて
English breakfast.
イングリッシュ・ブレックファースト
Alright!
いいわ！
Baek Seung Jo. Look forward to it!
ぺク・スンジョ 期待してなさいよ
Just like you, Oh Ha Ni.
やっぱり　オハニだな
Today's breakfast is the unrecognizable English breakfast.
今日の朝食は正体不明の イングリッシュ・ブレックファーストだな
Everything else is overcooked like crazy, but the beans are undercooked.
煮えてない豆以外は全部どうしようもなく焦げてる
I boiled them for a long time and they're still like that.
それは長時間煮たのにそんななの
You should have let them sit in water for a few hours beforehand.
煮る前に数時間水につけるもんだぞ
Oh!
え！
So this is the breakfast table of the new bride, Oh Ha Ni.
これがオ・ハニ若奥様の朝食の食卓か
What about coffee?
コーヒーは？
Coffee!
コーヒー！
The coffee tastes good.
コーヒーは美味しい
Sorry.
ゴメン
That's right!
そうだ
What is it?
何？
The lady gave it to me. She said to eat it with my hubby.
おばさんがくれたの旦那様とどうぞって
It's good. Try it.
美味しいわよ　食べてみて
Yours!
自分の
They say an apple in the morning is great! It's really good, right?
朝食にリンゴはいいって聞くわほんと美味しい　ね？
An apple and coffee on Sunday morning...
日曜の朝 リンゴとコーヒー
Not bad.
悪くないな
I'll really do well tomorrow.
明日はちゃんとするから
I've cleaned the whole house.
家中掃除したぞ
So...
だから－
The next course you've planned out.
おまえの準備した次のコース
Huh?
えっ？
Picking out my clothes. Oh, there was washing the blankets.
俺の服を選ぶあぁ　毛布洗いがあったな
Let's do that at night.
それは夜にしよう
You knew all about it?
全部　分かってたの？
Oh, this is it!
ああ　コレよコレ
English breakfast and coffee.
イングリッシュ・ブレックファーストにコーヒー
Great! It suits us perfectly!
いいじゃん私たちにぴったり
And... I'll do the shopping early in the morning,
それと　私が朝早くに買い物に行って－
and pick out the freshest produce!
一番新鮮なものを選んでくる
I'll come back and clean with Seung Jo.
帰ってきてスンジョと掃除して
I'll be a loved daughter-in-law and then...
愛される息子の嫁になるのそして・・・
Wash the blankets with the morning sunlight pouring down on us. With tons of bubbles!
朝日の降り注ぐ中で泡だらけになって毛布を洗うの
And once we're done, we'll go watch a movie.
それが終わったら映画を見に行くの
Oh, I'll pick out Seung Jo's clothes!
あっ！スンジョの服を選ぶ！
A style that matches the autumn sunlight!
秋の日差しが似合うスタイルのものをね
What'll look good?
何が似合うかな？
I'll search for it!
探してみよう
You think with your mouth. I couldn't ignore it even if I wanted to.
おまえしゃべりながら考えるだろ無視しようにも出来ないんだよ
We've got to go watch a movie.
映画見に行かなくちゃな
Yeah! Wait!
うん　待ってて
How is your outfit no different than mine?
おまえと俺のとどこが違うんだ？
Why?! It's pretty.
何でよ？可愛いじゃない
What's so pretty about it? Everyone is staring.
何が可愛いんだよじろじろ見られてるぞ
It's pretty.
可愛いじゃん
Hold on.
ちょっと待って
Hubby!
旦那様
What, wifey?
奥様　どうした？
Subtitles brought to you by the PKer team at Viki
Subtitles brought to you by the PKer team at www.Viki
Playful Kiss (Naughty Kiss) YouTube Version Episode 2 Preview
イタズラなキス　You Tube 版　第2話　予告
Here.
ほら
Practice. Injection practice.
点滴の練習しろよ
Just one more time and I think I'll definitely remember!
ちょっと待ってもう一回で絶対覚えるから！
Hey, what are you doing?!
おい　何するんだ?!